-德克萨斯州
- Texas.
现在我领先了
Now I'm in the lead.
-哦，那是我的
- Oh, that's mine.
-呃,呃!-是的
- Uh, uh! - Yeah.
从格林伯格出来-不
Coming out of Greenburg it pa- - No
-我们超过它了，它现在正从我们身边经过
- We passed it and it's passing us now.
-不，那不是德州
- No, that was not Texas.
这是格鲁吉亚
That was Georgia
那是一辆蓝色的货车
and it was a blue van
我记得很清楚
and I remember it distinctly.
-不,不
- No, no, no, no, no.
-你在偷我的盘子-没有
- You are stealing my plate. - No.
-连当地电视台都没有
- Not even a local station.
-嗯，最便宜的
- Well, the best bargains
都在最遥远的地方
are in the most far flung places.
-遥远的地方
- Far flung places.
哦，我讨厌那个广告
Oh, I hate that commercial.
啊，天气真好
Ah, such a pretty day.
-是的，女士
- Yes, ma'am, it is.
- 揍你?
- BEAT-NG-U'?
-打?
- Beating?
我才是那个领先的人
I'm the one that's in the lead.
-还是B-EAT-NG-U?
- Or is it B-EAT-NG-U?
哈哈，不管怎样，这是一个梳妆台，所以我要两份
Ha- ha, either way, it's a vanity plate, so I get doubles.
-天啊，嘿…
- Jeez, hey now...
-罗尼，他就快了!
- Ronnie, he's so close!
- 走啊
- Go around.
- Go around!
-我的天哪!
- My gosh!
你没事吧?
You okay?
唷,是的
- Phew, yeah.
-哦,亲爱的
- Oh dear.
那是同一辆卡车吗?
Is that the same truck?
-我不认为我们应该看到这个
- I don't think we were supposed to see that.
-这是怎么回事…?
- What in the name... ?
-哦!
- Oh!
他一定看见我们了
He must have seen us.
-他不可能
- He couldn't have.
-哦,不…
- Oh no...
-等等，亲爱的
- Hang on, honey.
-他在干什么?!
- What's he doing?!
-啊!
- Ah!
罗尼!
-Ronnie!
-他啊!哦，罗尼，小心点!
- What's he--ah! Oh, Ronnie, be careful!
-哦!哦!
- Oh! Oh!
-哦!
- Oh!
-你没事吧?
- Are you okay?
你对吧?
You all right?
-发生什么事了?
- What just happened?
-他早就走了
- He's long gone now.
就是个路霸
Just--just a road hog.
-哦…
- Oh...
-你没事吧?-哦,上帝
- You all right? - Oh, God.
-你在干什么?
- What are you doing?
-亲爱的，我要报警
- Honey, I'm gonna call this in to the police.
-什么?-好吧,是的
- What? - Well, yeah.
我们不能假装刚刚发生的事
We can't pretend that what just happened to us
没有发生在我们身上
didn't happen to us.
他们必须知道这件事
They gotta know about this.
-我不喜欢，罗尼
- Oh, I don't like it, Ronnie.
我一点也不喜欢
I don't like it one bit.
-是“我要打败你了?”
- Was it "I'M BEATING U?"
-我不知道
- I don't know.
-好吧，好吧，好吧
- Okay, all right, all right, all right.
我们去一个有电话的加油站
We're gonna go to a gas station where they have a phone.
好吧?好吗?
Okay? Okay?
我们要报警
We're gonna call this in.
-好吧?
- All right?
会没事的
It's going to be okay.
好吧，会没事的
Okay, it'll be okay.
-我想回家
- I wanna go home.
-我知道，亲爱的
- I know you do, honey.
好的
Okay.
-罗尼?
- Ronnie?
我们应该停下来看看床单是怎么回事
- We should stop and see what was going on with that sheet.
然后我们就可以把一切都告诉警察了
And then we can tell the cops all about it.
我们必须这么做，玛丽
We gotta do it, Marie.
-熟视无睹是不行的
- Turning a blind eye is not an option.
-爱你，宝贝
- Love you, baby.
-罗纳德·…
- Ronald...
-来吧
- Come on.
好吧，好吧，没事的
Okay, all right, it's all right.
-表……
- The sheet...
-是的
- Yeah.
录音:可怕的景象
recorded voice: The horrifying sight
警方认为罗恩和玛丽在那天目睹了
that police believe Ron and Marie witnessed that day
就是坑里那些臭名昭著的尸体
was the infamous bodies in the pit.
从那以后，罗恩和玛丽就再也没有出现过
Ron and Marie themselves have never been seen since.
又是一个来自南方深处的恐怖谜团
Just another macabre mystery from the deep south.
-那个视频你肯定看过很多遍了
- Surely you've watched that video so many times
你现在都记住了吗?
you have it memorized by now?
-不，是说真的
- No, real talk.
这真的发生了
This really happened.
其实就在这附近
Somewhere in this area, actually.
-拜托，这些事没解决是有原因的
- Come on, there's a reason those things are unsolved.
这都是神话和传说
It's all myths and legends.
在转动
Move over.
-不，这个YouTube视频已经过时了
- Nah, this YouTube video's out of date.
这是二十多年前的事了
This was from, what, twenty plus years ago.
现在这是…Ch-ch-ch……
Now this was... Ch-ch-ch...
-就像大脚怪，蛾人，春山杰克，
- Oh it's just like Bigfoot, Mothman, Springhill Jack,
卓帕卡布拉或者其他的
Chupacabra or any others.
-是啊，今晚你就能见到他们所有人的粉丝了
- Yeah, and you'll be meeting fans of all of them by tonight.
-真不敢相信我居然让你拉我来这个书呆子聚会
- I can't believe I let you drag me to this nerd fest.
-是吗?解释我这个
- Yeah? Explain me this.
这是真实的录像
Now, this is real footage.
即使你也不能否认
Even you can't deny it.
-你甚至看不见它
- You can't even see it.
有没有想过为什么那些证明视频总是摇摇晃晃的
Ever wonder why those proof videos are always shaky
浑浊，从不清脆清澈?
and murky, never crisp and clear?
-这是老了
- It's old.
爬行者每23年才回来一次
The Creeper only comes back every 23 years.
-地球是平的
- And the earth is flat.
纳粹在月球上扎营
Nazis are camped out on the moon.
猫王的生活
Elvis lives.
阿波罗着陆是伪造的…
The Apollo landing was faked...
-你宝贵的科学没有所有的答案!
- Your precious science doesn't have all the answers!
-阴谋论没有答案
- Conspiracy theories have no answers.
-你们一直都搞错了
- Y'all get it wrong all the time.
哥白尼,亚里士多德,ev -
Copernicus, Aristotle, ev--
不要这样做
Don't do that.
-牛顿，爱因斯坦，霍金?
- Newton, Einstein, Hawking?
-世界真大
- It's a big world.
奇怪的事情一直都在发生
Strange things happen all the time.
-两个字:奥卡姆剃刀
- Two words: Occam's razor.
这就是我成为科学家的原因
That's why I'm a scientist.
最简单的解释最有可能是正确的
The simplest explanation is most likely to be true.
-这也很简单，大脑互动体
- Well, this is also pretty simple, brainiac.
好了，爬行者回来了
All right, the Creeper comes back
每隔23个春天
every 23rd spring.
过了23天…
It kills for 23 days...
-然后呢?
- Then what?
-然后就消失了我不知道
- Then it disappears. I don't know.
-听起来像爱虫
- Sounds like a love bug.
它们是实验室里用来杀死蚊子的一种虫子
They were a breed of bugs made in a lab to kill mosquitos.
它们所做的就是交配和死亡
All they did was mate and die.
彻底的失败
Complete failure.
现在它们毫无用处
Now they serve zero purpose.
它们没有功能，
They have no function,
但它们每年会像风暴一样出现两次，
but twice a year they appear like a storm,
盲目追逐白色的东西
blindly chasing anything white
当他们接触到它的时候就会死亡
before dying when they come into contact with it.
-所以你认为爬行者是在实验室里制造的
- So, you think the Creeper was made in a lab.
-我觉得爬行者是在你脑子里造出来的，你个笨蛋
- I think the Creeper was made in your brain, you half-wit.
-爬行者是不会交配的
- Well, the Creeper doesn't mate.
它会杀死……
It kills...
据说它杀死了几百人，甚至几千人
It's said to have killed almost hundreds, maybe thousands.
-等等，他们不是把它拍成电影了吗?
- Wait, didn't they make a movie out of it?
变态爬行者还是什么?
Creepy Creeper or something?
-其实是三个，但都不是真的
- Three actually, but none of that is real.
它是以一个俗气的洛杉矶有线电视节目命名的…
And it was named after a cheesy LA cable access show...
宝贝?宝贝!
Baby? Baby!
莱恩!
Laine!
-宝贝，我告诉过你玉米煎饼会回来的
- Baby, I told you that burrito would come back
困扰你
to haunt you.
好吧，你知道我打字很烂
all right, you know I suck at typing.
我今晚就去问她
I'm gonna ask her tonight.
我拿到戒指了，所以…
I've got the ring so...
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
我爱你，妈妈
I love you, Mom.
-怎么了，姑娘?
- What is up girl?
你好吗?
How are you?
-一切都很疼，我快死了
- Everything hurts and I'm dying.
-哦，很好吧?
- Oh, that good, huh?
-你还好吗?
- Ew, are you all right?
-对我来说太晚了，救你自己吧
- It's too late for me, save yourself.
-你考试了吗?
- So, did you take the test yet?
-我把它带来了
- I brought it with me,
但我认为这是积极的
but I think this counts as a positive.
-你总是那么乐观
- You are always the optimist.
-我不是这个意思，你知道的
- Not at all what I meant and you know it.
-嗯，我想等我到的时候再说
- Well, I was trying to hold it till I got there,
但我要撒尿，裁缝，我的士兵间谍
but I need to tinkle, tailor, my soldier spy.
我待会再打给你
I'm gonna have to call you back.
-我听不进去
- I'm not hearing this.
到了酒店给我打电话，好吗?
Just call me when you get to the hotel, okay?
记得别吐在那些空军一号上
Oh, make sure that you do not puke on those Air Force Ones.
-别拿这个开玩笑
- Don't even joke about that.
-莱恩，我什么时候拿时尚开玩笑过?
- Laine, when have I ever joked about fashion?
-萨姆，我发誓如果你给我施了恶咒
- Sam, I swear if you jinxed me,
我发誓我会…
I swear to God I'll...
-莱恩，我爱你，但你得给我多买几双鞋
- Laine, I love you, but you're buying me some more shoes.
靠……
Fuck...
我看起来像是为丛林而生的吗?
Do I look like I'm built for the woods?
-你带我到最迷人的地方
- You bring me to the most charming places.
提醒我一下我们为什么在这里?
Remind me why we're here again?
-宝贝，我等不及带你去看看这个地方了
- Baby, I can't wait to show you this place.
-你确定我们应该来这里吗?
- Are you sure this is where we're supposed to be?
-是啊，我们应该很接近
- Yeah, we should be close.
现在你知道我们要去哪里了…
Now you know that's where we're going...
-真的吗?
- Really?
-马尼拉夫人，你怎么能不呢?
- Lady Manilla, how could you not?!
嘿，也许她会给你看手相
Hey, maybe she'll read your palm.
是啊!
Yeah!
-相信你能找到最奇怪的人
- Trust you to find the strangest
问路的地方
place to ask for directions.
-该死，看看这些酷东西
- Damn, look at all this cool stuff.
-我不明白
- I don't get it.
走吧，蔡斯，没人，我们走
Come on, Chase, nobody's here, let's go.
蔡斯，别碰所有东西
Chase, don't touch everything.
你吓死我了!
You scared the shit out of me!
-看看这个
- Take a look at this.
我不知道他们在离海岸这么远的地方捕鲸
I didn't know they had whaling this far from the coast.
-有什么你喜欢的吗?
- Anything strike your fancy?
-我们在找这个地址
- We're looking for this address,
但我在地图上都找不到
but I can't find it on any map.
-啊，地图上没有
- Ah, it's not on any maps.
卫星有点坏了
The satellites are kind of screwed up
我想是在我们小镇上空
over our town I guess.
在那里
There.
我们在这里
And we are here.
走68号公路往南走5英里
Just take 68 five miles to south
看到标志时向左转
and turn left when you see the signs.
-呃,谢谢
- Uh, thanks.
-没有问题
- No problem.
一共50美元，可以吗?
That'll be $50 please?
- 50,\n- 50--
-这是古董，亲爱的
- It's antique, honey.
古董
Antique, okay.
-听着，你随时都可以回来
- Now you come back any time, you hear.
哦，恭喜你们俩
Oh, and congratulations to you both.
哦，他不知道?
Oh, he doesn't know?
她也不知道
Neither does she.
有趣
Interesting.
-好吧，这是…
- Okay, this was, er...
-我们有一棵结果的树
- We have a tree bearing fruit.
他会非常高兴的
He will be most pleased.
-哇，看这个
- Wow, look at this.
这地方就我们两个吗?
Are we the only ones in this place?
-宝贝…
- Babe...
等
Wait there.
我还有一个惊喜给你
I've got another surprise for you.
-蔡斯，你要去哪?
- Chase, where are you going?
-嘿，我是萨姆
- Hey, this is Sam.
我只是在忙着过最好的生活
I'm just busy living my best life.
-萨姆，你到底在哪儿?
- Sam, where the hell are you?
-什么事?
- What is it?
-这是你的惊喜
- It's your surprise.
-你说真的吗?
- Are you serious?
那些是什么?
What are those?
-我们要玩cosplay
- We're gonna cosplay.
你和我
You and me.
我把需要的东西都带来了
I brought everything we need.
你要做的就是选择你想成为的人
All you need to do is choose who you wanna be.
-我不会穿的
- I'm not putting on any of them.
-什么?
- What?
-是的…
- Yeah...
是啊，反正这主意也太蠢了
Yeah, I mean it was a stupid idea anyway.
我是说，我知道你不会穿这些东西
So, I mean, I knew you wouldn't wear some of this stuff.
反正也很俗气，所以我不想让你穿
It's tacky anyway, so I don't even want you to wear it.
也许我会穿它
Maybe I'll wear it.
我不知道
I do not know.
-我能看吗?-不!
- Can I watch? - No!
-《恐怖猎犬2021》现场直播
- Coming to you live from Horror Hound 2021.
我是卡莉，我来找最大的爬行者…
I'm Carrie and I'm here to find the biggest Creeper...
-嘿，莱恩，他们在说爬行者
- Hey Laine, they're talking about the Creeper.
YouTube视频里的那个
The one in the YouTube clip.
-所以，小丑装能告诉我更多
- So, clown outfits tell me more.
-他们说小丑很吓人
- Well, they say that clowns are frightening
但我说我们都是好的
but I say that we are everything good
生活中所有的坏事
and bad in life all at once.
-看看这些小丑们的爱…
- Look at all the love the clowns...
-妈咪要把这些街道涂满鲜血
- Mommy's gonna paint these streets with blood.
-在我们的
- Stumbling around in our
破旧的小社区…
little old and shattered community...
-试试这个
- Try this on.
-猜猜还有谁会出现…
- And guess who else might turn up...
-好的，J先生
- Okay, Mr. J.
-没错，当地的恐怖传说，爬行者
- That's right, local horror legend, the Creeper.
-既然我满足了你的粉丝幻想，
- Now that I've satisfied your fanboy fantasies,
你要穿什么?
what are you gonna wear?
-什么?哦,这样
- What? Oh, this.
-t恤吗?
- A T-shirt?
-不是普通的t恤
- Not just any T-shirt.
这件t恤
This T-shirt.
-我该拿你怎么办?
- What am I gonna do with you?
-莱恩? !
- Laine?!
宝贝，你没事吧?
Baby, you all right?
它只是一只鸟
It's just a bird.
吓死我了
Scared the crap out of me.
宝贝……
Babe...
让我们开始…
Let's start going...
这是派对时间
It's party time.
来吧
Come on.
-我不知道会有这么多人参加
- I had no idea so many people attended these things.
-这是cosplay界的科切拉
- This is the Coachella of cosplay.
-是啊，对变态杀手来说
- Yeah, for psycho killers.
看起来像一群杂耍鬼
It looks like a gathering of juggalos.
-拜托，你喜欢疯狂小丑团
- Oh please, you love Insane Clown Posse.
我看过你的Spotify
I've seen your Spotify.
-离我的手机远点，你这个跟踪狂!
- Stay off my phone you stalker!
-天使回答说
- And the angel answered and
对百姓说，
said unto the people,
你们不要惧怕，因为我知道你们寻求
fear not, ye, for I know ye seek
弥赛亚
the Messiah.
因为它已经复活了
For it is risen.
所有喊:哈利路亚!
all shout: Hallelujah!
-我很确定正确的说法是“他复活了”
- I'm pretty sure the correct phrase is, "He is risen."
-耶稣基督!
- Jesus Christ!
没错，欢迎来到恐怖猎犬!
That's right, welcome to Horror Hound!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
-这些人真的很糟糕
-these people are really fucked up.
-你真该看看你的脸-勾，线，沉
- You should have seen your face--hook, line, and sinker.
-嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿
- Hey, hey, hey, hey,
-尿裤子了
- Shitting their pants.
他们脸上的表情
The looks on their faces.
糟了
Shit.
-他们在美化真正的杀手
- They are glorifying actual killers
你真的不介意吗?
and you're honestly okay with that?
-没有……
- No...
不,他们不是
No, they're not.
这一切都只是为了好玩
It's all just for fun.
-如果人群中潜伏着一个疯子怎么办?
- What if there's a psycho lurking in the crowd?
你怎么知道?
How the hell would you know?
-宝贝，没有疯子
- Baby, there's no psychos.
只是一群人在玩
Just a bunch of people having fun.
-即使是大型音乐节也有人数统计
- Even big music festivals have a body count.
我不敢想象这里是什么样子
I dread to think what it's like here.
人山人海，每个人都在喝酒、聚会、开车……
Crowds of people, everyone drinking, partying, cars...
-锋利的东西
- Sharp things.
-追逐…
- Chase...
好吧，我去拿饮料
Okay, I'll get the drinks.
嘿
Hey.
-我他妈现在就在做
- I'm doing that right freaking now.
-牌子上写着“关门”
- The sign says "closed."
追逐!
Chase!
-你割伤了自己，先生?
- You cut yourself, Sir?
-抱歉各位，我有事耽搁了
- Sorry folks, I got held up
为今晚的大演出做准备
preparing for tonight's big show.
特效之类的
Special effects and such.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
五比三，从中间挑
It's three for five, pick them from the center.
-可以吗?-太棒了
- Is that all right? - Great.
-从这里?
- From here?
-在中间
- In the center.
中心-好吧，酷
Center. - All right, cool.
宝贝，退后，看我工作!
Baby, stand back and watch...me...work!
这是近了!
That was close!
我要用另一只手，好吗?
I'm gonna use my other hand, okay?
宝贝,你在看吗?
Babe, you watching?
好吧，这是我最后一个了
Ah, okay, it's my last one.
-你喜欢吗?
- You like that?
-我从没见过这样的事
- I've never seen anything like this.
-那是因为它们都是独一无二的
- That's because they're all unique.
每一个手工制作的
Each one handmade.
爬虫的风格
Creeper style.
你听说过爬行者吗?
You ever heard of the Creeper?
-别让他开口
- Don't get him started.
-就像当地的传说，对吧?
- It-- it's like a local legend, right?
每23年就杀死数百人?
Kills hundreds of people every 23 years?
-差不多吧
- Something like that.
-我告诉…
- I told...
-现在你试试
- Now you try.
-我吗?
- Me?
不，不
No, no, no, no, no.
不-你要这么做
No, no, no, no, no. - You're doing this.
你要这么做你这样做
You are doing this. You're doing this.
来，这边走
Come on, this way.
-成功向人类目标投掷刀片
- Successfully throwing blades at a human target
是一种艺术形式
was an art form.
现在，首先你找到你的投掷线…
Now, first you find your throwing line...
就是这个
That's this.
好了，现在是成功投掷的关键
Okay, now the key to successfully throwing
刀锋是你和目标之间的距离
a blade is the distance between you and the target.
现在，如果你找到了投掷线，
Now, if you've found your throwing line,
你得往后退一步
you're gonna take a step back.
然后向左转45度
And you're gonna turn 45 degrees and to your left.
好了，现在你要走到那条线上
Okay, now you're gonna step up to that line
然后像扔棒球一样扔出去
and throw it just like a baseball pitch.
尽你所能
Hard as you can.
什么!
What!
宝贝，这太变态了!
Baby, that was sick!
这和爬行者有什么关系?
So, how is this related to the Creeper?
-他们说这些是他最喜欢的玩具
- They say these are some of his favourite toys.
-似乎是低效的
- Seems inefficient.
-为了延长追捕时间
- To prolong the hunt.
有一个小缺点
There is the minor drawback that
即使你达到了目标
even if you hit your target,
你扔掉你的武器
you throw away your weapon.
你需要别的东西来完成任务
You need something else to finish the job.
或者如果爬行者像蔡斯那样投球，那他就需要
Or if the Creeper throws like Chase, then he would need it.
-她今天有笑话
- Oh, she got jokes today.
-噢!啊,该死的
- Ow! Ah, damn it.
-我知道了，我知道了只是割伤，只是割伤
- I got it, I got it. Just a cut, just a cut.
-童子军
- Boy Scout.
总是做好准备
Always be prepared.
-你们要来参加大型爬行者抽奖吗?
- You guys coming to the big Creeper Draw?
-有什么吸引力?
- What's the draw?
-午夜前开始
- Starts just before midnight after
主舞台上的角色扮演表演
the cosplay show on the main stage.
你们一定要去看看
You guys should definitely check it out.
谁知道呢，说不定你还能赢呢
Who knows, you might even win.
宝贝，没事的，只是划伤
Baby, it's all right, it's a cut.
-你没事吧，公主?
- Are you all right there, Princess?
-快点，快点你对吧?
- Come on, come on. You all right?
-嘿，你是来参加爬行者抽奖的吧?
- Hey, you're here for the Creeper Draw, right?
知道布伦特在哪吗?
Any idea where Brent is?
有人看见布伦特了吗?
Has anybody seen Brent?
任何人吗?
Anybody at all?
他已经做过箭的特技了吗?
Did he do the arrow stunt already?
-那个箭男?
- The arrow guy?
我们拍摄了他我们录下来了，对吧，麦奇?
We filmed him. We got it on tape, right Mikey?
-是啊，是啊，都录下来了
- Yeah, yeah, it's on tape.
-那他到底在哪儿?
- Well then, where the hell is he?
我是说我们五分钟后就要上台了
I mean we're supposed to be on stage in five minutes.
好吧，布伦特会为此挨揍的
All right, Brent's gonna get his ass kicked for this.
听着嘉莉,
Listen Carrie,
恐怕这次你得一个人来了
I'm afraid you're gonna have to do this one alone.
布伦特不在，而且都快半夜了
I mean, Brent's not here and it's nearly midnight.
来吧，我来教你怎么做
Come on, I'll show you the ropes.
很容易-完美
It's easy. - Perfect.
杰米，帮我拿东西好吗?
Jamie, grab my stuff please?
-你要做的就是…
- What you're gonna do is you're just gonna...
-在我继续之前能给我来杯姜茶吗?
- Oh, can I get a ginger tea before I go on?
-不，你绝对不能
- No, you absolutely cannot.
-好吧!
- All right!
谢谢你的节目，性感版的杰森
Thank you for the show, uh, sexy version of Jason, I think.
不管怎样,恭喜
Anyway, congrats.
-嘿，来吧，我们去看看这个
- Hey, come on, let's check this out.
我们的爬行者抽奖时间到了!
It is time for our Creeper Draw!
-我们的大奖得主是前环球小姐，
- And revealing our grand prize is former Miss Universe,
公主的黑暗,
Princess of Darkness,
我们的司仪……
our Master of Ceremonies...
夫人大屠杀!
Madame Carnage!
-安静，你们这些乡巴佬!
- Silence, you peasants!
我周游世界，把恐惧注入
I have travelled the world injecting fear into
你们这些凡人的心
the hearts of mere mortals like y'all.
但我们来这里是为了一件非常非常特别的事，
But we are here for something very, very special,
恐怖猎犬节
the Horror Hound Festival.
这是我的魔鬼孩子
It's the devil child of my making
因为它回到了我的精神家园
'cause it's back in my spiritual home
杰克逊,路易斯安那州!
of Jackson, Louisiana!
-这个地方历经千古
- The very place that through the ages
我们引诱和吞噬
we have lured and devoured
像你们这样悲哀的灵魂
sad souls like y'all.
来吧，屠杀!
Come on now, carnage!
-告诉我们大奖是什么
- So, tell us what the grand prize is.
-两个人的逃生室，爬行者主题
- An escape room for two, Creeper themed.
你们这些恐怖的小怪物住的鬼屋
A haunted little house for all you creepy little freaks.
-没错，变态，倒霉的赢家
- That's right, creeps, the unlucky winners
我们的大抽奖将被随意抽取
of our grand draw will be taken at will
到历史悠久的巴纳贝特故居
to the historic Barnabett house
在那里你会渴望令人不安的神话
where you will thirst for disturbing myths.
血腥恐怖将被考验到极限
And the bloody macabre will be tested to the limit
在一个与众不同的逃生室里
in an escape room with a difference.
还有网络红人…
Accompanied by internet sensation...
-你听到她说的了
- There, you heard her.
爬行者是真的!
The Creeper's a real thing!
-我想没人知道她在说什么
- I don't think anybody knew what she was talking about.
但好吧，我承认，这是小众的
But okay, I give you that, it's niche.
还有一些人也相信这一点，
And there are other people that believe it too,
所以你也不完全是个怪胎
so you're not a complete freak after all.
-你喜欢现在的每一秒，不是吗?
- You're loving every single second of this ain't you,
你大书呆子吗?
you big nerd?
-我更喜欢生物学家-哦,是的
- I prefer biologist. - Oh, yeah.
-现在，要选出优胜者，
- And now, to draw the winner,
杰克逊自己的马尼拉夫人!
Jackson's very own Lady Manilla!
数字……
Number...
5……
5...
1……
1....
4！
4!
-天啊，那是我-什么?
- Oh my God, that's me. - What?
-这怎么可能?我从来没有赢过任何东西
- How is that possible? I never win anything.
-这是巫术，宝贝
- Its voodoo, baby.
514是我们!
514 is us!
-是的!
- Yeah!
好吧!
All right!
那边那个帅哥就是我们的冠军!
That handsome guy over there is our winner!
-你能相信吗?谢谢!
- Can you believe this? Thanks!
-记住，如果你在黎明前离开，
- And remember if you get out by daybreak,
你将赢得一个特别奖
you'll win a special prize.
-现在，为我们的获胜者鼓掌
- Now, round of applause for our winner.
到后台来，我们马上就会让你们开始!
Come on backstage and we'll get you guys going in no time!
-太棒了
- That was amazing.
-这边，小心你的头
- Right this way, just watch your head.
-你真的想这么做吗?我的意思是……
- Do you really wanna do this? I mean...
-是爬行者的房子!
- It's the Creeper house!
关于爬行者的事我都知道
I know everything there is to know about the Creeper.
我们很快就能离开那里
We'll be out of there in no time.
-是啊，我知道，但是…相信我,相信我!
- Yeah, I know, but... Trust me--trust me!
-恭喜你，这边请
- Congratulations, right this way.
穿过这里就到了
It's just through here.
我们在那
There we are.
-好的，在这里和这里签名
- Okay, just sign there and there.
-这些是什么?-标准发布表格
- Uh, what are these? - Standard release form.
我们可以永远使用你的形象，
We get to use your image forever and ever,
在宇宙中
ever in the universe.
如果出了什么差错，我们不负责
We're not liable if anything goes wrong.
就像平常的废话，废话，废话
The usual blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
-为什么?
- Uh, but why?
-哦，对不起，我忘了介绍我自己了
- Oh sorry, I forgot to introduce myself.
我是制片人杰米
I'm Jamie, the producer
她的表演
of her show.
我们要拍下这一切
We're coming along to film all this.
这是我们和音乐节协议的一部分
It's part of our deal with the festival.
-嘿，莱恩，我们要上电视了!
- Hey Laine, we're gonna be on TV!
-上网，不是看电视
- Internet, not TV.
-甚至更好我的迹象
- Even better. Sign me up.
-好吧!就在那边，小姐
- All right! Just down there, Miss.
在你自己的时间
In your own time.
好了，好了，队员们，出发!
Okay, all right, team, let's go!
让我们移动它!
Let's move it!
-嘿，赢家
- Hey there, winner.
-我是凯莉-凯莉
- I'm Carrie. - Carrie.
-很高兴见到你
- Nice to meet you.
-莱恩，那个流口水的混蛋是蔡斯，我男朋友
- Laine, the drooling jerk is Chase, my boyfriend.
我们怎么去那里?
How are we gonna get there?
-斯图会带我们去，跟我来
- Uh, Stu's going to take us there, so follow me.
“跟我来”
- "Follow me."
-你最好是对的
- You'd better be right about
让我们尽快离开那里
getting us out of there quick sharp.
-宝贝，来吧
- Baby, come on.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我不敢相信这一切发生了
I can't believe this is happening.
恐怖之神是站在我们这边的
The horror gods are on our side.
-蔡斯，那个人不是…
- Chase, isn't that the guy...
-你想看看这个吗?
- You wanna take a look at this?
-这是什么?
- What am I looking at?
-伙计们，我们真的要坐那玩意去吗?
- Guys, are we really going there in that thing?
-别担心，他看起来有点吓人
- Don't worry, he looks a little bit creepy,
但他是个好人
but he's a sweetheart.
-一点?
- A bit?
去吧，上车
Go on, get in.
-嘿，想被一个疯乡巴佬杀了吗?
- Hey, wanna get killed by a crazy redneck?
因为你就是这样被杀的
Because that's how you get killed.
-来吧，你们两个
- Come on, you two.
我爱你
I love you.
-你准备好迎接恐怖之夜了吗?
- Are you ready for the big night of terror to begin?
-我们还剩十秒!
- We've got ten seconds to go!
: 10 !\nall: 10!
9 !\n9!
8 !\n8!
: 7 !\nall: 7!
6 !\n6!
: 5 !\nall: 5!
: 4 !\nall: 4!
3 !\n3!
2！
2!
1！
1!
放点音乐吧，外面的人都快疯了!
- Hey, play some music, the crowd's going wild out there!
-网络断了，伙计-那就做点什么!
- The internet dropped, man. - Well, do something!
-好了，伙计们，wi-fi断了，但别担心
- All right, folks, we're out of wi-fi, but never fear.
一个好的DJ出门一定要带几张黑胶唱片!
A good DJ never leaves the house without a few vinyls!
-你打算一路上都不跟我说话吗?
- So you're not gonna talk to me for the whole journey?
吗?-那是什么?
At all? - What is that?
- B卷
- B-roll.
-那是什么?
- What is that?
-宝宝…-影子?
- Baby... - Shadow?
-你能至少看着我吗?
- Can you at least look at me?
-我不确定它看起来像个爬行者
- I'm not sure. It looks like a Creeper.
-等等，等等，你是想告诉我
- Wait, wait, wait, you mean to tell me
你录下爬行者了吗?
you got the Creeper on tape?
这是真实的录像?
This is real footage?
-嗯，爬行者
- Well, a Creeper.
可能是某个玩cosplay的混蛋
It's probably just some asshole in great cosplay.
-真的吗?
- Or is it?
-决议是什么?
- What's the resolution on that?
-原生4k，为什么?
- Native 4k, why?
-看到了吗?
- See?
清爽、清晰的光学效果没有任何区别
Crisp, clear optics makes no difference.
-太棒了
- Great.
-如果那个叫约翰的人失踪了
- If that John guy turns out to be missing
我们可能有线索
we might have something.
这是有趣的
This is interesting.
-哦,是的
- Uh, yeah.
我猜我是用手机点燃的吧?
So I guess I light this using cellphones?
-欢迎来到巴纳贝特家族墓地
- Welcome to the Barnabett family cemetery.
这是最后的安息之地
This was the final resting place
为了回到18世纪的灵魂
for souls back to the 1700s.
当地人认为这里是圣地
The natives believed that this was holy ground.
回到人类的黎明
Back to the dawn of man.
神圣的
Sacred.
但是非常非常闹鬼
But very, very haunted.
-太棒了
- Awesome.
我想知道我能不能葬在这里
I wonder if I could be buried here.
-小心你的愿望
- Uh, be careful what you wish for.
-闭嘴
- Shut up.
-我们怎么又来了?
- What are we doing here again?
我们不是该去鬼屋什么的吗?
Weren't we supposed to go to the haunted house or something?
-是的
- Yeah.
我们从这里走过去
We walk from here.
-看到了吗?
- You see that?
-怎么了?来吧，我们一定要拿到这个
- What's wrong? Come on, we gotta get this.
-相机坏了
- Camera won't work.
我不晓得
I dunno.
-不，不，不，不知道是不够的，伙计
- No, no, no, dunno ain't gonna cut it, pal.
我给你钱不是让你扳倒摄制组的
I didn't pay you to bring the film crew down
为我的健康干杯
to Whistling Dixie for my health.
你说没用是什么意思?
Now what do you mean it won't work?
它不能打开?它不会专注?
It doesn't turn on? It won't focus?
不记录?不操自己?
Won't record? Won't fuck itself?
我在这里做什么?
What am I even doing out here?
-没人想听起来像他那样
- See, now, nobody wants to sound like that guy.
-我得了艾美奖，该死的
- I have got an Emmy, God damn it.
莱恩-莱恩!
- Laine--Laine!
-我才不在乎你的艾美奖呢
- I don't give a fuck about your Emmy.
摄像机坏了又不是我的错
It's not my fault the camera doesn't work.
-莱恩!
- Laine!
-你去死吧
- You can go fuck yourself.
-你有时候真是个混蛋
- You're such an asshole sometimes.
-莱恩!
- Laine!
-宝贝，一切都好吗?
- Babe, is everything all right?
-我不知道，你说呢
- I don't know, you tell me.
一切都好吗?
Is everything all right?
-什么意思?
- What do you mean?
-我知道这里面有蹊跷
- I know there's something going on there with that
金发小妞和你
blonde bimbo and you.
说实话，我一点也不介意
Honestly, it doesn't bother me.
我只是觉得它太“有趣”了
I just find it so "interesting."
-哦，得了吧
- Oh, come on.
我都没注意到她!-真的吗?
I didn't even notice her! - Really?
“太棒了，请把我埋在这里，我是个荡妇!”
"Awesome, bury me here please, I'm a bimbo!"
你想让我给你个杯子接口水吗?
You want me to give you a cup to catch your drool?
-不，我没那么说
- No, I didn't say it like that.
这是不公平的
And that's not fair.
莱恩!
Laine!
-不，真的，我爱她
- No, really, I love her.
她很深沉，我知道
She's deep, I get it.
-拜托，我…
- Come on, I...
-你好吗?
- Hello?
嘿，你是参加音乐节的吗?
Hey, are you with the festival?
是我,迈克尔!
It's me, Michael!
相机的家伙,
The camera guy--
你有电话吗?
Do you have a phone?
我只是需要一点系绳
I just need a bit of a tethering
为了把我的东西放到网上
in order to get my stuff online.
听着，我只需要用一会儿
Look, I only need it for a bit.
我的制片人会杀了我的
My producer's gonna kill me
如果我现在不把这些东西放到网上
if I don't get this stuff online right now.
-你好吗?
- Hello?
-靠!
- Fuck!
奶个熊……
Well shit...
-你在找什么，你的班卓琴吗?
- What are you looking for, your banjo?
- 上帝,伙计 -靠!
- Jesus, man--fuck!
你的脸!
Your face!
我太逊了
Oh, I did pee myself a little.
-现在我们可以走了
- Now we can go.
其他人呢?
Where are the others?
-迈克尔?迈克尔!
- Michael? Michael!
-那没脑子的东西去哪了?
- Where has that no good shit for brains gone to?
这绝对是我和他最后一次合作了
This is definitely the last gig I'm working with him.
-我是YouTuber，让我离开这里!
- I'm a YouTuber, get me out of here!
-啊，没什么!
- Ugh, it was nothing!
我只是想看看录影机上有什么…
I just wanted to see what was on that vide...
等等，等等，等等，等等……
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
你嫉妒了
You're jealous.
-我没有嫉妒-你嫉妒
- I'm not jealous. - You're jealous.
它是可爱的
it's cute.
-嫉妒是弱智的表现
- Jealousy is the sign of a weak mind.
-那么，女人的笑话
- So, bimbo jokes.
等待,宝贝…
Wait, baby...
莱恩……
Laine...
-不!
- No!
-也许有什么东西抓住了他?
- Maybe something got him?
像个大动物
Like a big animal.
-这附近没有大型动物
- There are no big animals 'round here.
-拜托，这是路易斯安那州!
- Come on, this is Louisiana!
有像…
There's like...
鳄鱼、蛇和
gators, snakes and
到处都是黑熊
black fucking bears roaming all around.
-他们不会来的
- They wouldn't come here.
-莱恩!
- Laine!
莱恩!
Laine!
-莱恩!-嘿,男人!
- Laine! - Hey man!
嘿，嘿，伙计，放轻松!
Hey--hey, man, take it easy!
这是怎么呢你的女朋友在哪里?
What's going on? Where's your girlfriend?
-有些……
- Some...
大的东西了……
Something big took...
-我告诉过你，该死的黑熊!
- I told you, black fucking bear!
熊不会飞
- Bears don't fly.
冷静点，伙计
Now calm down, man.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
-我们得走了我们得走了，报警
- We have to go. We have to go, call the police.
-什么?
- What?
-快他妈的叫警察!
- Call the fucking police!
-哦,他妈的!
- Oh, fuck!
这是迈克尔,哦!
It's Michael--oh!
让他的东西
Something got him.
-它是新鲜的真的很新鲜
- It's fresh. Really fresh.
如果他被什么东西抓走了，肯定还在外面
If something got him, it's still out here.
-在里面快!
- Inside. Quick!
-莱恩!
- Laine!
-哦，小心
- Oh, be careful.
这是座老房子，你不知道里面有什么
It's an old house, you dunno what's in here.
-打开!-上帝该死!
- Open up! - God damnit!
-打开!-上帝该死
- Open up! - God damnit.
-现在都是你的了头里
- They're all yours now. -Come on.
-加油!他妈的闭上!
- Come on! Fucking shut!
-来吧，你们这些混蛋!-打开!
- Come on, you assholes! - Open up!
-该死的!
- God damn it!
-搞什么鬼?
- What the fuck?
来吧!
Come on!
他妈的闭上!
Fucking shut!
-这就是你的逃生室吗?
- So this is your escape room, huh?
你这是在玩什么游戏吗?
Is this some kind of game you're playing here?
因为你可以停止表演，打开门
'Cause you can stop the show and open the door.
我们都很害怕你的乡巴佬把戏
We're all very scared of your hillbilly tricks.
-闭上你的臭嘴
- Shut your fuckin' mouth.
打开!
Open up!
这不是我想要的
I didn't sign up for that.
迈克尔死了，你们都看到了
Michael's dead and you all saw it.
快他妈的把门打开
Now open that fucking door.
-你对莱恩做了什么?
- What did you do with Laine?
她在哪里!
Where is she!
冷静下来
Calm down.
我不知道，好吗?
I don't know, all right?
我根本就不应该出现在这里!
I wasn't even supposed to be here!
雇我来就是为了吓吓你
All I was hired to do was scare ya up a bit.
这是所有
And that's all.
-雇佣吗?
- Hired?
受雇于谁?
Hired by who?
-吉塞尔…
- Giselle...
马尼拉
Manilla.
她说有个惊喜在等着你
She said there's a surprise waiting here for you.
-一个惊喜吗?
- A surprise?
-我给你个他妈的惊喜
- I'll show you a fucking surprise.
你现在告诉我莱恩在哪，否则
You tell me where Laine is right now or
我会把这东西插进你屁股里，
I'll stick this thing so far up your ass,
你会尝到该死的滋味
you'll taste the fuckin' metal.
-是啊，乡巴佬，该说话了
- Yeah, hillbilly, it's time to start talking.
-你们都他妈的往后退一步!
- All of you take a step fuckin' back!
-哇，哇，哇!
- Woah, woah, woah!
-不然我就打爆你的头!
- Or I'll blow your fuckin' brains out!
-我的耳朵在嗡嗡叫!
- My ears are fucking ringing!
-我警告过你!退一步!
- I warned you! Step back!
-天啊，斯图，你没必要开枪的!
- Jesus, Stu, you didn't have to fire that thing!
-下次我再这么做，你就什么都听不到了
- Next time I do, you won't hear anything anymore.
-好吧，我们来解决这个问题
- Okay, let's figure this out.
这是个逃生室，对吧?
It's an escape room, right?
-这他妈不是逃跑的地方
- It's not a fucking escape room.
这是一个陷阱
It's a trap.
-谁是猎人?
- And who's the trapper?
-爬虫
- The Creeper.
爬行者是个童话，孩子
The Creeper's a fairytale, son.
-我看到了
- I saw it.
-你们都他妈疯了
- You guys are fucking nuts.
-它抓走了莱恩，我会找到她的
- It's got Laine and I'm gonna find her.
-我们原地不动-什么?
- We're staying put. - What?
别告诉我，这打乱了你繁忙的日程
Oh, don't tell me, this interrupts your hectic schedule
乡下乡巴佬乱伦和断断续续的爱马
of country hick incest and intermittent horse loving.
-去你的，好莱坞
- Fuck you, Hollywood.
我们得开始团队合作了
We've gotta start working as a team.
虽然我知道这对你来说很困难，
So as difficult as I know it is for you,
我要你别再像个混蛋一样!
I need you to stop being a fuckin' asshole!
你被我们困住了
You're stuck with us now.
把它下来
Put it down.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
在我找到莱恩之前谁都不能走
Nobody's going anywhere until I find Laine.
-它的到来
- It's coming.
楼上,现在!
- Upstairs, now!
-去阁楼!
- Go to the attic!
-我们在外面的时候，我看到这里有光
- When we were outside, I saw a light in here.
我去找个开关
I'll find a switch.
屋顶在漏水
The roof is leaking.
-但是没有下雨
- But it's not raining.
-你一定是在逗我!
- Oh, you gotta be shitting me!
那是谁啊?
Who the hell is that?
-这是山姆……
- That's Sam...
-那是什么鬼东西!
- Oh, what the hell is that?!
-你是真实的
- You're real.
-她在哪里!
- Where is she!
她在哪里!
Where is she!
离开我!
Get off me!
跟我聊天!
Talk to me!
离开我!
Get off me!
-帮助!
- Help!
追逐!
Chase!
救命!
Help!
-她去哪了?
- Where the hell did she go?
-她一定在这附近
- She's gotta be here somewhere.
-走吧，嘉莉!
- Come on, Carrie!
凯莉!
Carrie!
-操
- Fuck.
-凯莉!嘿,嘿
- Carrie! Hey, hey.
-它来了-它来了!
- It's coming--it's coming!
莱恩-莱恩在哪儿在哪儿?
Where's Laine--where's Laine?
-我不知道-她在哪里?
- I don't know. - Where is she?
莱恩在哪里?-我不知道
Where is Laine? - I don't know.
我不知道-她在哪里?
I don't know. - Where is she?
-那是什么?
- What's that?
-在这里…
- In here...
在这里
In here.
走吧!来吧
Go! Come on.
-没有出路了
- There's no way out.
-我们得杀了它
- We're just gonna have to kill it.
-是的，用擀面杖
- Yeah, with a rolling pin.
-行不通它是不朽的，相信我
-It won't work. It's immortal, trust me.
我们唯一的希望就是它对我们失去兴趣，
Our only hope is it loses interest in us,
或者我们等着捕猎周期结束
or we wait out the hunting cycle.
-捕猎周期有多长?
- And how long is the hunting cycle?
- 23天
- 23 days.
-我们受骗的
- We're fucked.
我们是失败的
We are fucked.
-我真的有一种déjà似曾相识的感觉
- I'm getting a real sense of déjà vu.
-莱恩!
- Laine!
莱恩!
Laine!
-莱恩，是我!
- Laine, it's me!
是我，是我，是我
It's me, it's me, it's me.
莱恩,请,谢谢!是我，宝贝，是我
Laine, please, please! It's me, baby, it's me.
宝贝,发生了什么?-我们得离开这里!
What happened, baby? - We have to get out of here!
-你怎么了?
- What--what happened to you?
-他会抓到你们的!
- He'll get you all!
所有靠近我的人
Anyone who's near me.
-宝贝，你在流血-它想要的是我
- Baby, you're bleeding. - It's me it wants.
-唯一的出路是上楼
- The only way out is upstairs.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们走吧!
Let's go!
-大家团结起来
- Everybody stick together.
-我抓住你了，我抓住你了
- I got you, I got you.
-哦，电话!-等等!
- Oh, the phone! - Wait!
哦,他妈的!哦,我的腿!
Oh, fuck! Oh, my leg!
哦,哦,他妈的!No-ho-ho !
Oh--oh, fuck! No-ho-ho!
哎呀,我的腿!
Agh, my leg!
哦,他妈的!
Oh, fuck!
911有什么紧急情况?
911, what's your emergency?
先生，您的位置在哪里?
What's your location, sir?
-我们到底在哪里?
- Where the hell are we?
-巴纳贝特之家-巴纳贝特之家!
- The Barnabett House. - The Barnabett House!
先生?-是的
Sir? - Yeah.
先生，有什么问题吗?
What's the problem, sir?
---爬虫有东西想要杀死我们
- The--the--the Creeper. Something is trying to kill us.
你吸毒了吗?
Have you been taking drugs...
先生?
Sir?
-我听起来像他妈的瘾君子吗?
- Do I sound like a fuckin' stoner to you?
我需要你去巴纳贝特之家找人帮忙
I need you to get some help to the Barnabett House
否则我对天发誓
or I swear to God...
先生，你没事吧?
Sir, are you okay?
-操!-来吧，我们走!
- Fuck, please! - Come on, let's go!
我们走吧!来吧!
Let's go! Come on!
-抓住他，抓住他!
- Hold him, hold him!
-哎呀!
- Agh!
-加油!
- Come on!
-哦,狗屎!
- Oh, shit!
,快,快
- Quick, quick.
-宝宝…
- Baby...
-等等,什么?你为什么停下来?
- Wait, what? Why are you stopping?
-即使我们出去了我们也会成为靶子
- Even if we get outside we're sitting ducks out there.
-帮我一下
- Help me over here.
-我们是冒险还是躲在这里?
- Do we risk it or hole up in here?
-我赞成蹲下
- I vote hunker down.
警察来了，这样爬行者就会慢下来
The police are coming, so that will slow the Creeper down.
-是吗?
- Are they?
-他们不会无视报警电话的，对吧?
- Well, they're not just gonna ignore a 911 call, right?
-哦，我可爱的夏天的孩子
- Oh, my sweet summer child.
-哦，操，我他妈的需要个医生!
- Oh fuck, I need a fucking doctor!
-我们就像蜘蛛网里的苍蝇
- We're like flies in a spider's web.
它在发号施令
It's calling the shots.
结束这一切的唯一方法就是杀了它
The only way we end this is to kill it.
-你男朋友说不行，所以…
- Well, your boyfriend said we can't, so...
-我不太确定
- I'm not so sure.
我近距离看过
I've seen it up close.
-如何呢?
- How then?
-它又老又破
- It's old and decrepit.
它散发着死亡的气息
It stinks of death.
-那它到底在哪里?
- Well, where the hell is it, anyway?
-它在耍我们
- It's toying with us.
他喜欢玩
He likes to play.
-我们得把它困住
- We need to trap it.
-什么?
- With what?
-凯莉!-跑!
- Carrie! - Run!
-操!
- Fuck!
-去，抓住他!
- Go, take him!
-凯莉!-哎呀!
- Carrie! - Agh!
-凯莉!
- Carrie!
凯莉!来吧!
Carrie! Come on!
-不!
- No!
不!
No!
-快-快!来吧!
- Quick--quick! Come on!
-这里，这里，这里!
- Here, here, here!
-快!
- Quick!
-搞什么鬼
- What the f--
-圣母玛利亚
- Holy Mary, mother of God.
为我们这些罪人祈祷现在和我们死的时候，阿门
Pray for us sinners now and at the hour of our death, amen.
-阿门
- Amen.
-这是什么地方?
- What is this place?
-你能看见什么?
- What can you see?
-耶稣!
- Jesus!
-哦,操
- Oh, fuck.
-好像没了
- Looks like it's gone.
凯莉
It took Carrie.
-哦,不不,耶稣!
- Oh no. No, Jesus!
哦,他妈的
Oh, fuck.
不，主啊，不要这样
No, please, Lord, not like this.
-不，不是这样
- No, not like this.
-也许这里有东西能帮到我们
- Maybe there's something in here that can help us.
也许，呃，信息或者…
Maybe, erm, information or...
-不管怎样，我们都逃不掉了
- One way or another, we're done running.
-是的,确实
- Yeah, literally.
-我不明白这地方怎么
- I don't understand how this place
还没烧成平地
isn't burnt to the ground yet.
-好吗?-哦,史—
- Please? - Oh, shi--
-我愿意用我的左臂换…
- I'd give my left arm for...
-小心点，你可能会
- Careful, you might.
-是啊，我马上就后悔说了那些话
- Yeah, I instantly regretted saying that.
-对不起人是啊，只是紧张
- Sorry man. Yeah, it's just nerves.
-那是什么鬼?
- What the hell is that?
巫毒娃娃吗?
Voodoo doll?
-什么…
- What the...
-耶稣的圣子
- Holy son of Jesus.
-伙计们，石头
- Guys, the stone.
-宝贝,等待……
- Baby, wait...
-天啊，他们在喂它
- Oh my God, they're feeding it.
-宝贝，你为什么说他在追你?
- Baby, why did you say he was after you?
它把你带到哪里去了?
Where did it-- where did it take you?
到底发生了什么?-蔡斯，我怀孕了
What really happened? - Chase, I'm pregnant.
所以它才来找我
That's why it's after me.
-什么?
- What?
-它想要我拥有的东西
- It wants what I've got.
是的……
And, yes...
我愿意嫁给你……
I will marry you...
如果我们能活着出去
If we ever get out of here alive.
-但他们为什么要喂这东西?
- But why the hell would they be feeding this thing?
看看这些垃圾
Look at all this crap.
这是什么?
What is this?
神社吗?
A shrine?
-我以为这些是故事
- I thought these were stories.
传说
Legends.
但这一切似乎都是真实的
But it all seems real.
-还有什么，它有一个狂热的粉丝俱乐部
- And what, it has a cult fan club
这能养活它吗?
that helps feed this thing?
也许他们想要我们中的一个
Then maybe they want one of us.
-什么?
- What?
-我们无法抵抗
- We can't fight it.
但我们可以打败它，甚至阻止它
But we can beat it, maybe even stop it.
我们现在就在它扭曲的网里
We're in its twisted web right now.
但是时候扭转局面了
But it's time to turn the tables.
我们需要一个计划
We need a plan.
-我想我知道我们该怎么做了
- I think I know what we need to do.
走，走……
Go, go, go, go...
斯图!
Stu!
我抓住他了，我抓住他了!
I've got him, I've got him!
-来吧，混蛋!
- Come on, asshole!
把孩子带走，他的生命力属于你
Take the baby, its life force belongs to you.
长生不老，把孩子带走
Live forever, take the baby.
它的生命力属于你
Its life force belongs to you.
长生不老，把孩子带走
Live forever, take the baby.
它的生命力属于你
Its life force belongs to you.
-你不能拿走!
- You can't have it!
-来吧
- Come on.
-你喜欢那些偷窥者吗，贱人?
- How do you like those peepers, bitch?
-现在!
- Now!
-哦,不
- Oh, no.
-下车!
- get off!
下车!
Get off!
-斯图,不!
- Stu, no!